My name is Doğukan; I work in İzmir in Litum as a front-end developer.
I have a personal project named Flexible Grid System.
You can reach this open source project at Github.
Actually, It's only a Grid System version of Bootstrap and using this, people can develop websites very fast.
They can manage the design in smartphones, tablets and desktops very fast with that website they made.
Besides, there is also another framework that I develop.
This framework will help rapid designing as well.
Besides of that, I currently keep developing Flexible Grid System
It has approx. 1000 stars in Github.
You must take look at it, you must!
It will help you, it will spare your time and provide speed and flexibility.
You can check it out and follow it from flexible.gs address.
Thank you.